http://www.nicoletcollege.edu/about/compliance/privacy-policy

View PDF
Nicolet College is committed to ensuring your privacy as a visitor to this website.
When you browse through the Nicolet College website, certain information is collected in relation to your computer's IP (Internet Protocol) address.  We automatically collect and temporarily store the following information about visits from IP addresses:
date and time of visit
pages visited
browser used and screen resolution
search terms used
originating website
We may use this information for statistical purposes and to help us make our site more useful to visitors.  No additional information is collected unless otherwise stated.
Nicolet College does not require that you provide personal information to visit our website. You may choose to provide personal information to us through web forms, email, or live chat. Any personally identifiable information provided will be used only for the purposes you authorize or in support of college-sponsored programs. These purposes may include providing relevant materials, products, and services, and facilitating your relationship with the college. Information you provide may be shared with other persons within the college. Information you provide may be shared with other persons within the college who have a legitimate educational interest or in compliance with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974, as amended.
Nicolet College does not disclose, give, sell or transfer any personal information about our online visitors to third parties except as required by law. The Nicolet College website contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. These links are provided only for the convenience of our visitors.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a data file that is created and stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit our website, and it allows our website to identify your web browser, for example.  cookies facilitate user preferences, allowing a website to remember the user.  Cookies can also be used in order to allow for our website to function properly.
How We Use Cookies
We use cookies to track how our users access and use the services offered on our website, to learn when and how users visit the website, to learn which search terms are used, and to learn which websites direct you to the Services. We also use cookies to help display certain information about Nicolet College services and to improve your enjoyment and convenience when using or visiting the website.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies.  You can decide if and how your web browser will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser.  You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your web browser. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, we will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our website.
If you have questions or concerns regarding the Nicolet College privacy policy, please email webmaster@nicoletcollege.edu
Nicolet Live!
